

#### $\searrow$

becirevicahmed@gmail.com

П

+38761949104

9

Sarajevo

aboutme.ahmed.games/

in

linkedin.com/in/ahmedbecirevic

github.com/ahmedbecirevic

## **SKILLS**























## **LANGUAGES**

#### Enalish

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

## Bosnian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### German

Limited Working Proficiency

# PERSONAL SKILLS

Problem solving

Planning strategically

Attention to detail

## Ahmed Bečirević

Second-year IT student at International Burch University. I am highly passionate about coding and technology. Looking forward to upgrading my knowledge in the software engineering field, gain new experiences and connections. I have worked on designing MySQL databases, worked on data structures and algorithms in Java, and I am currently developing a full-stack application (PHP, Flight PHP, jQuery). Please visit my GitHub repository linked on the left side of this document for more insight into my previous work.

## **EDUCATION**

## Information Technologies - Undergraduate

International Burch University

08/2020 - Present

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## **TeamUP Startup Co-founder**

**IBU Startup Incubator** 

03/2021 - Present

TeamUP is a startup driven to change the teambuilding activities in BiH.

## Internship On Project RutMap BetaTelStudio

12/2020 - 02/2021

Achievements/Tasks

Directional mapping of 360 photos.

## Football Judge

Udruženje fudbalskih sudija i instruktora Kantona Sarajevo

03/2019 - 05/2019

## **CERTIFICATES**

MTA: Introduction to Programming Using Python (06/2020)

## PERSONAL PROJECTS

## CarDiaries

- Full stack web application intended to bring car enthusiasts together.
- Backend: PHP, Flight PHP, MySQL (organized in three layers DAO, BLL, application).
- Frontend: jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.
- □ To visit website click here.

## CarDiaries Mobile - Android

Mobile version of the web app above in Android.

#### TeamUP Website

- Static website with information about my startup.
- □ To visit website click here.

### About Me Website

- Static website made for practice.
- □ To visit website click <u>here</u>.

#### Linux Shell

□ Simple shell implementation done in C.